<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alan&#39;s Analysis</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alan&#39;s Analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m great at two things: making jokes and making graphs. This site is for my jokes.
Clearly.
Growing up on a small, isolated, Idahoan farm is a challenge. A challenge I&amp;rsquo;ve never had to face thankfully. And while I did grow up in Idaho, I have no more knowledge of potatoes than the next person (FYI it&amp;rsquo;s called the gem state, not the potato state). I&amp;rsquo;ve been a few places, gotten a few degrees, and had a few experiences worth converting into visually appealing graphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2nd Degree Burns</title>
      <link>/post/2nd-degree-burns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2nd-degree-burns/</guid>
      <description>Now that I’ve graduated college for the second time, I’ve moved on to a job that really doesn’t have anything to do with what I studied. Out of the team I’m currently a part of, almost everyone else has formal experience/knowledge/degrees in statistics, math, psychology, etc. As such, some people ask me what I studied (BBA Finance/Management &amp;amp; MS Finance) and what those degrees entail. And while it’s only been a few months since I traded my classes for meetings, I really can’t remember the overall picture – only specific projects or presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1,000 Miles in my Shoes</title>
      <link>/post/1-000-miles-in-my-shoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/1-000-miles-in-my-shoes/</guid>
      <description>Every day I begrudgingly get out of bed, shower, put on some clothes (ideally), and go out the door to face the day’s challenges. But no matter what life throws at me, I’ll always know just how far I walked in a day, thanks to my phone’s pedometer! Since I got it in October 2016, my phone has dutifully kept track of just how many steps I’ve taken. For better or worse, it only tracks steps I’ve physically taken, and not any improvements or regressions in my personality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relationshipping &amp; Handling</title>
      <link>/post/relationshipping-handling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/relationshipping-handling/</guid>
      <description>In my first post, I showed how many of my high school classmates are now engaged, married, or have a kid. And in light of some recent events, I thought I might as well dive into my own relationship history to see if there is anything to see from an analytical perspective.
It all started my Senior year of High School, when I tailored my appearance enough to become what I call “dateable from a looks perspective”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Life&#39;s got You Blogdown</title>
      <link>/post/when-life-s-got-you-blogdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/when-life-s-got-you-blogdown/</guid>
      <description>Somebody asked me how I made this website when I’ve made it clear to them in the past that I know nothing about website design. “Like anyone else!” I said. “By making a deal with an ethereal void-being who promised forbidden knowledge at little to no cost to me!”
HTML actually stands for ‘Here take my life’In all seriousness, I got lucky with how this all worked out. I use a program called R extensively in the work I do, and wouldn’t you know it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Graph Seen &#39;Round My Graduating Class</title>
      <link>/post/the-graph-seen-round-my-graduating-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-graph-seen-round-my-graduating-class/</guid>
      <description>It’s been 5 years since I graduated high school. There were about 1,200 students in total when I left, and I graduated with 286 other young adults eager to do something with our lives. If facebook is any indicator though, that something was to get married and/or have kids as soon as possible. It’s eastern Idaho; what can you expect?
So many Mormons is what you can expectNaturally, this can slightly (read: really) bum you out if you think you’re in the minority of not being one of those people who have found their life partner or have had their mini me before 23.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>