<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alan&#39;s Analysis</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alan&#39;s Analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m great at two things: making jokes and making graphs. This site is for my jokes.
Clearly.
Growing up on a small, isolated, Idahoan farm is a challenge. A challenge I&amp;rsquo;ve never had to face thankfully. And while I did grow up in Idaho, I have no more knowledge of potatoes than the next person (FYI it&amp;rsquo;s called the gem state, not the potato state). I&amp;rsquo;ve been a few places, gotten a few degrees, and had a few experiences worth converting into visually appealing graphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Graph Seen &#39;Round My Graduating Class</title>
      <link>/post/the-graph-seen-round-my-graduating-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-graph-seen-round-my-graduating-class/</guid>
      <description>It’s been 5 years since I graduated high school. There were about 1,200 students in total when I left, and I graduated with 286 other young adults eager to do something with our lives. If facebook is any indicator though, that something was to get married and/or have kids as soon as possible. It’s eastern Idaho; what can you expect?
So many Mormons is what you can expectNaturally, this can slightly (read: really) bum you out if you think you’re in the minority of not being one of those people who have found their life partner or have had their mini me before 23.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>